qoinpro.com 2017-09-10

# Free Bitcoins, free Litecoins, free Feathercoins - QoinPro.com

## __Privacy Policy (Last updated: January 27, 2014)

Our privacy policy is displayed below. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which QoinPro.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of QoinPro.com. By becoming a member you acknowledge to have read this privacy policy and agree to it. 

* * *

#### PRIVACY POLICY

QoinPro.com values Privacy. Users' privacy is very important to QoinPro.com and we are committed to safeguarding all information that was entrusted to us. The website of QoinPro.com is not directed to children under the age of 13. 

#### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

QoinPro.com may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. QoinPro.com may also collect information about how Users use our website, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the website or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" or "sessions" to track how Users use our website. A cookie is a piece of software that a web server can store on the Users PC and use to identify the User should they visit the website again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our website. 

#### HOW WE USE INFORMATION

QoinPro.com may use personally identifiable information collected through our website to contact Users regarding products and services offered by QoinPro.com and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users' experience with QoinPro.com and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. 

QoinPro.com may also use information collected through our website for research regarding the effectiveness of the website and marketing, advertising and sales efforts of QoinPro.com, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. 

#### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

QoinPro.com may disclose information collected from Users to trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners who will use the information for the purposes outlined above. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. We may also transfer information collected from Users in connection with a sale of QoinPro.com's business. Finally we may release information upon request from law enforcement agencies, when the law requires us to do so or at our sole discretion in dispute situations. 

#### MAINTENANCE OF INFORMATION

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure. 

#### FINAL WORD

This privacy policy may be available in multiple languages. In the event of a discrepancy between the versions, the English version prevails and takes precedence. 

#### QUESTIONS

Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to [support@qoinpro.com](mailto:support@qoinpro.com) or through our Support Desk at: [http://support.qoinpro.com](http://support.qoinpro.com/).
